Let's see who dares kick me out
I'm carrying a Jiang heir
He's your grandson
Could you bear to see him out on the streets?
Stop acting, you old hag
At your age
how could you possibly get pregnant?
We're at a hospital
How could I lie?
Son, I'm begging you
I'm already ruined
The Jiang family's only heir
Get up
I exposed my husband's affair with the maid
and was killed for it
This life
your whole family will pay in blood
Xiaolan, come
Come wash my feet
Zhang Guifen, don't push it
Oh my
My precious son says
he wants Grandma serving him personally
If she doesn't serve well
he won't come out
He'll stay in there
Let's see who panics
You little darling
Honey
Honey, calm down
Careful of the baby in her belly
If not for that belly
carrying a Jiang heir
I'd have thrown you out long ago
Don't hurt the baby
Something's wrong
That look in Jiang Chengang's eyes
It's not how you look at a daughter-in-law
Oh, Chengang
Gently
I'm carrying your child
Don't crush him